

# JOHNNY NGUYEN

## Career Objective

Computer Science student pursuing an internship to further improve my programming knowledge. With my solid knowledge of C++ and Java, I am a diligent worker that strives to learn more from experienced team members while providing my knowledge.

## Education

## Metropolitan Community College – Kansas City

Associate in Computer Science

August 2020 – May 2022 Kansas City, MO

## University of Missouri - Kansas City

Bachelor of Science in Computer Science

August 2022 – May 2024 Cumulative GPA: 3.79

## **S**kills

- Java
- C++

#### Familiar with:

- Python
- Assembly

## Experience

### **KC Energy Project**

Creator

April 2023 - May 2023

- Coded a java program that allowed users to enter in data from a customer that allowed the user to access and manipulate the data that entered
- Multiple functions that allowed the user to check the customer's bills, payments, creating an invoice, and has a dashboard with all these functions.

## UMKC Asian Students in America *Organization member*

August 2022 - Present

- Attends events ran by A.S.I.A with the purpose of connecting with other Asian-identifying students
- Learns about other Asian ethnicities to broaden perspective and knowledge on diverse cultures

## Relevant courses

- Data Structures
- Data Communication
- Networking
- Algorithms and Complexity
- Operating Systems

## Awards

- Deans List (Spring 2023)
- Chancellor's Transfer Award
- A+ Scholarship (Fall 2020 Spring 2022)
- Dr. Jerrald F. Stach Memorial Scholarship